export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt:"1.Who is the father of Computers?",
        optionA:" James Gosling",
        optionB:" Charles Babbage",
        optionC:"Dennis Ritchie",
        optionD:"Bjarne Stroustrup",
        answer:"B",
    },
    {
        prompt:"2.MS-Word is an example of ____?",
        optionA:"An operating system ",
        optionB:"A processing device",
        optionC:"Application software",
        optionD:"An input device",
        answer:"C",
    },
    {
        prompt:"3.Ctrl, Shift and Alt are called _____ keys?",
        optionA:"Modifier",
        optionB:" Function",
        optionC:" Alphanumeric",
        optionD:"Adjustment",
        answer:"A",
    },
    {
        prompt:"4.Junk e-mail is also called ______?",
        optionA:"Spam",
        optionB:"Spoof",
        optionC:"Sniffer Script",
        optionD:"Spool",
        answer:"A",
    },
    {
        prompt:"5.Microsoft Office is an example of a?",
        optionA:"Closed source software",
        optionB:"Open source software",
        optionC:"Horizontal market software",
        optionD:"vertical market software",
        answer:"C",
    },
    {
        prompt:"6.Where is RAM located?",
        optionA:"Mother Board",
        optionB:"Expansion Board",
        optionC:"External Drive",
        optionD:" None",
        answer:"A",
    },
    {
        prompt:"7.In MICR, C stands for____?",
        optionA:"Code",
        optionB:"Colour",
        optionC:"Computer",
        optionD:"Character",
        answer:"D",
    },
    {
        prompt:"8.A computer consists of____?",
        optionA:"motherboard",
        optionB:"hard disk drive",
        optionC:"hard disk drive",
        optionD:"  All of the above",
        answer:"D",
    },
    {
        prompt:"9.A____is approximately one billion bytes",
        optionA:"Megabyte",
        optionB:"Gigabyte",
        optionC:" Terabyte",
        optionD:" None of these",
        answer:"B",
    },
    {
        prompt:"10.Which file starts MS Word?",
        optionA:"word.exe",
        optionB:"msword.exe",
        optionC:"word2003.exe",
        optionD:" winword.exe",
        answer:"D",
    },
]